怎么林师弟认得此人
师兄此人便是我家那个傻子世子
原来是个傻子呀
怪不得还带着一条狗
傻子也陪露天宗听这笑话呀哈哈哈
这里可不是狗窝
识相的带着你的狗干净
看来上次给海少的教训不够好
怎么又想体验断手之聪了
少说废话
本少的伤已经被师尊治好了
更是破而后立
一举达到了重积极境界
而我不过就是一个小小的练气气
多说一句
扒了你的皮啊肃静
给我小心一点
石城林家林洋想要加入天宗
这师兄此人不是来参加天宗的
他这纯粹是来捣乱的
老九
你认识此子
当然认识此子此子心胸狭隘
废了我的徒儿
谁要是收他入门
那就是和老婆作对啊
呃
那既然如此你便离开吧
我们天宗
是不会受你这种品行低劣的弟子
天宗曾经也是巅峰一时的人界宗门
按道理应该广纳贤才
为何不给我个机会
哈哈哈哈哈
你也知道我天宗乃是人间第一大宗
我们只收天骄
不收你这样的废物
你怎么知道我不是天骄
哈哈哈
别走
那我今天就让你看看什么是天骄
什么竟然是8级天赋
8级天赋
如今在天宗之内
也只有大长老是8级天赋
其他长老就只有7级天赋
没想到又出现了一个八级天骄
老九
没想到你在石城居然捡了个宝宝
哈哈哈哈二师兄您见笑了
哈哈哈林师弟的确天赋卓越
甲乙十日必定成为天宗的中流体著
嗯野种
睁开你的狗眼看看
这就是天骄和你之间的境界
的区别哈哈哈
我还以为有多厉害
不过是一个区区8级天赋吧
哈哈那你上去试试啊
本尊的资质凭一个雕像还不够测的
大胆狂徒
你说什么
How did Junior Brother Lin recognize this person?
Senior brother, this person is the fool prince of my family
He was a fool
No wonder he brought a dog with him
A fool also accompanies the Open Air Sect to listen to this joke, hahaha
This is not a kennel
Take your dog clean sensibly
It seems that the lesson given to Young Master Hai last time was not good enough
Why do you want to experience the Satoshi of Broken Hands again?
Cut the crap
This young master's injury has been healed by the master
It's even more broken
In one fell swoop, he achieved a state of heavy positivity
And I'm just a little Qi training
Say more
Peel your skin, be quiet
Be careful here
Shicheng Lin Family Lin Yang wants to join Tianzong
This senior brother is not here to participate in Tianzong
He's just here to make trouble.
Lao Jiu
You know him?
Of course I know this son, this son is narrow-minded
Abolish my apprentice
If anyone accepts him for entry
Is that against your wife?
Ah.
If that's the case, you can leave.
Our Tianzong
I will not accept a disciple with inferior conduct like you
Tianzong used to be a peak human sect
It stands to reason to recruit talents
Why don't you give me a chance?
Hahahaha
You also know that my Tianzong is the largest in the world
We only accept Tianjiao.
Don't accept trash like you
How do you know I'm not arrogant?
Hahaha
Don't go
Then I will show you what Tianjiao is today.
What is a level 8 talent?
Level 8 Talent
Now in Tianzong
Only the Great Elder is a level 8 talent
Other elders only have level 7 talent
Unexpectedly, another level-eight genius appeared
Lao Jiu
I didn't expect you to pick up a baby in Shicheng
Hahahaha Second Senior Brother, you are laughing
Haha, Junior Brother Harlin is indeed talented
A and B will definitely become the middle fluid of Tianzong in ten days
Hmm, bastard.
Open your dog's eyes and take a look
This is the realm between Tianjiao and you
The difference hahaha
I thought it was amazing
It's just a level 8 talent
Haha, then you go up and try it.
The qualifications of the deity are not enough to be tested by a statue
daring madman
Pardon me?